module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What name did Sam\'s crush and his mother have in common?', 
    a: 'Carol',
    b: 'Karen',
    c: 'Jasmine',
    d: 'Joanna',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What singer did Harry make fun of Karen for enjoying?', 
    a: 'Cher',
    b: 'Dolly Parton',
    c: 'Joni Mitchell',
    d: 'Joan Jett',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The actor who played movie stand-in, Jack, was also in what hit series?', 
    a: 'Game of Thrones',
    b: 'Sherlock',
    c: 'Psych',
    d: 'True Detective',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the title of the song that Billy Mack sang?', 
    a: 'Jingle Bell Rock',
    b: 'Christmas is All Around',
    c: 'Chestnuts Roasing on an Open Fire',
    d: 'Baby, It’s Cold Outside',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was David, the Prime Minister, related to?', 
    a: 'Karen',
    b: 'Juliet',
    c: 'Sarah',
    d: 'Harry',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where in America did Colin go?', 
    a: 'Texas',
    b: 'California',
    c: 'Wisconsin',
    d: 'DC',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What language did Jamie learn to woo Aurelia?', 
    a: 'Spanish',
    b: 'Portuguese',
    c: 'Turkish',
    d: 'Italian',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What dessert does Juliet offer Mark?', 
    a: 'Bread Pudding',
    b: 'Chocolate Cake',
    c: 'Gingerbread',
    d: 'Banoffee Pie',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What celebrity did Daniel have a thing for?', 
    a: 'Bridget Bardot',
    b: 'Kate Moss',
    c: 'Marilyn Monroe',
    d: 'Claudia Schiffer',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Natalie’s occupation at 10 Downing Street?', 
    a: 'Secretary',
    b: 'Housekeeper',
    c: 'Caterer',
    d: 'Assistant',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];
